import React from "react"
import './question.css';
const questions=[
    {question: "What is a correct syntax to output 'Hello world' in java?",
        options:["System.out.println(\"Hello World\");","echo(\"Hello World\");","print(\"Hello World\")","Console.WriteLine(\"Hello World\")"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question:"Java is short for \"JavaScript\"",
        options:["False","True",],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?",
        options:["//This is a comment","/*This is a comment","#This is a comment",],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "Which data type is used to create variable that should store text?",
        options:["String","Txt","myString","string"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
        options:["float x=5;","x=5;","int x=5;","num x=5"],
        answer:2,
    },
    {question: "How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
        options:["byte x=2.8f","byte x=2.8f","int x=2.8f","float x=2.8f"],
        answer:3,
    },
    {question: "Which method can be used to find the length of a string?",
        options:["length()","getLength()","getSize()","len()"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "Which operator is used to add together two values?",
        options:["THe * sign","The + sign","The & sign"],
        answer:1,
    },
    {question: "The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.",
        options:["False","True"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
        options:["toUpperCase()","upperCase()","tuc()","touppercase()"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
        options:["=","><","==","<>"],
        answer:2,
    },
    {question: "To declare an array in Java, define the variable type with:",
        options:["{}","[]","()",],
        answer:1,
    },
    {question: "Array indexes start with",
        options:["0","1"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "How do you create a method in Java?",
        options:["()methodName","methodName.","methodName[]","methodName()"],
        answer:3,
    },
    {question: "Which keyword is used to create a class in Java?",
        options:["class()","MyClass","className","class"],
        answer:3,
    },
    {question: "What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?",
        options:["new myObj - MyClass()","MyClass myObj = new MyClass();","class myObj = new MyClass();","class MyClass = new myObj();"],
        answer:1,
    },
    {question: "In Java, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.",
        options:["False","True"],
        answer:1,
    },
    {question: "Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
        options:["Math.max(x,y)","Math.largest(x,y)","Math.maxNum(x,y)","Math.maximum(x,y)"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "Which operator is used to multiply numbers?",
        options:["%","#","x","*"],
        answer:3,
    },
    {question: "Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?",
        options:["lib","import","package","getlib"],
        answer:1,
    },
    {question: "How do you start writing an if statement in Java?",
        options:["if(x>y)","if x>y then:","if x>y:"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "How do you start writing a while loop in Java?",
        options:["While(x>y)","x>y while{","while x>y{","while x>y:"],
        answer:0,
    },
    {question: "Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
        options:["get","void","return","break"],
        answer:2,
    },
    {question: "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
        options:["break","exit","return","stop"],
        answer:0,
    },
]
export default questions;